bfi0.com 2006-04-26

# Epsilon Interactive: Privacy Policy

We Respect Your Privacy

Privacy Policy

**The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the Epsilon Interactive Web site.**

_Any and all information collected at this site, via your permission, will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed unless legally required. Any information you provide on the Epsilon Interactive Web site will be held with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways for which you have not given consent. A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard your personal information is described below._ [](http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.bigfootinteractive.com&sealid=103)

**Access to Information**  
All information is secure and may be accessed only by key staff members of Epsilon Interactive. 

**Browser Information Collected on This Web Site**  
Epsilon Interactive analyzes our Web site logs (e.g. IP address, referring urls) to constantly improve the value of the materials available on our Web site. Our Web site logs are not personally identifiable, and we make no attempt to link them with the individuals that actually browse the site. 

**Changes to Your Profile**  
If you would like to update your information please go to the **Contact Us** window and submit a new form with updated contact information. Any Profile updates or changes will take place within a 24 hour period. 

**Links**  
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Epsilon Interactive is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Epsilon Interactive. 

**Notification of Changes**  
This policy was last reviewed in May of 2004. Changes were limited to: update of contact information; information on our enrollment into the TRUSTe Privacy Program; information on our enrollment in the Safe Harbor Program. If we decide to revise our privacy policy, we will post a notice of those revisions on our Homepage and disclose the changes in this privacy statement. If, however, we are going to use user's personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.

Epsilon Interactive takes stringent precautions to protect information from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. 

**Privacy Concerns**  
If you have any concerns regarding our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us via email at [privacy@epsiloninteractive.com](mailto:privacy@epsiloninteractive.com). 

**Privacy of Email Lists**  
Epsilon Interactive maintains an email marketing newsletter list (PROfile) to communicate with our clients and prospects. Individuals must affirmatively ask to join our mailing list by opting in on the Epsilon Interactive Web site. We do not sell, rent, loan, trade or lease the addresses on our list to anyone. All email messages sent to this list include an opportunity to unsubscribe or opt-out of this list. 

**Resale or Disclosure of Information to Third Parties**  
Epsilon Interactive does not sell, rent, loan, trade or lease any personal information collected on the Epsilon Interactive Web site, including email lists, without prior consent.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site. 

**Security**  
Epsilon Interactive does not request sensitive information (such as a credit card number and/or social security number) from our users. We take every precaution to protect our users' information both online and offline. Periodically, our employees are notified about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our clients' information is protected. The servers on which we store data are kept in a secure environment. If you have any questions about the security at our Web site, you can send an email to [privacy@epsiloninteractive.com](mailto:privacy@epsiloninteractive.com). 

**Use of Cookies**  
We do not use cookies on this site.   
_Epsilon Interactive is strongly committed to upholding the highest level of privacy and permission standards._

* * *

Epsilon Interactive Clients

Epsilon Interactive works with the world's leading marketers to create permission-based email marketing programs that achieve superior results. 

Epsilon Interactive's role in supporting our clients may include hosting the actual collection site, delivery of email, tracking results of email campaigns, analysis of data, and transferring collected data back to the client. Epsilon Interactive is contractually bound to keep our clients' customer data private and this data is never shared across clients. 

Some of our clients use Epsilon Interactive's email marketing technology platform to design and send their own campaigns. We have a stringent policy against sending unsolicited commercial email. If problems arise with a client's campaign, we will work with the client to resolve the problems and prevent them in the future. If Epsilon Interactive determines that a client has knowingly used our system for sending unsolicited commercial email, we will immediately revoke the client's permission to send email using our product or our system. 

Internet user privacy is very important to Epsilon Interactive and our clients. The protection of consumers' information and privacy is a vital part of our business. 

Before companies can use Epsilon Interactive technology to send email, they must commit to us in writing that consumers have agreed to receive such email messages. 

Epsilon Interactive is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. Questions, concerns, comments and complaints can be addressed to [privacy@epsiloninteractive.com](mailto:privacy@epsiloninteractive.com). 

TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. For more information on TRUSTe, please [click here](http://www.truste.org/). Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to users' privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. 

If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should first contact Epsilon Interactive's Privacy Administrator by email at [privacy@epsiloninteractive.com](mailto:privacy@epsiloninteractive.com). 

If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been addressed to your satisfaction, you can then contact [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/users/users_watchdog.php). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison to Epsilon Interactive for prompt complaint resolution. 

* * *

Safe Harbor

The collection of personal information by businesses is governed by Directive 95/46/EC of the European Parliament and of the Council of 24 October 1995 on the protection of individuals with regard to the processing of personal information and on the free movement of such information, as well as the national legislation of European Union Member states. For more information, see <http://europa.eu.int/comm/internal_market/privacy/index_en.htm>. 

Epsilon Interactive enters into processing contracts with its clients in the EU that specify that the EU client recognizes that it is a data controller for the purposes of data protection legislation and therefore it will need to be in compliance with the relevant Member State national law. Any data processed by Epsilon Interactive is not further disclosed to third parties, except where required by the European client as a data controller or when required by law. Any information that our EU clients identify as sensitive will be treated as such. 

Epsilon Interactive has a Privacy Administrator who is responsible for the internal supervision of Epsilon Interactive privacy policies and a team of technicians to handle data security. Epsilon Interactive educates its employees about compliance with the Safe Harbor Principles and has self-assessment procedures in place to ensure its compliance. [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/) serves as Epsilon Interactive's third-party dispute resolution provider. 

We participate in the EU Safe Harbor Privacy Framework as set forth by the United States Department of Commerce. As part of our participation in the safe harbor, we have agreed to TRUSTe dispute resolution for disputes relating to our compliance with the Safe Harbor Privacy Framework. If you have any complaints regarding our compliance with the Safe Harbor you should first contact us. 

If contacting us does not resolve your complaint, you may raise your complaint with TRUSTe by: 

  * Internet – <http://www.truste.org/users/users_watchdog.php>;
  * Mail – WatchDog Complaints, TRUSTe, 685 Market St., San Francisco, CA, USA 94105; or
  * Fax – 415-618-3420.

If you are faxing or mailing TRUSTe to lodge a complaint, you must include the following information: 
  * The name of company
  * The alleged privacy violation
  * Your contact information
  * And whether you would like the particulars of your complaint shared with the company.

For information about TRUSTe or the operation of TRUSTe's dispute resolution process, see [http://www.truste.org/users/users_watchdog_intro.html](http://www.truste.org/users/users_watchdog.php) or request this information from TRUSTe at any of the addresses listed above. The TRUSTe dispute resolution process shall be conducted in English.
